http://www.heelsforyou.com/index.php?main_page=privacy

Welcome,
My Account
Your cart is empty.
Wide Width High Heels
X - Large Heels (sizes 15-17)
* CLEARANCE *->
Wedge Sandals
Steampunk Style
Accessories
...
Specials ...
New Products ...
Featured Products ...
All Products ...
Your cart is empty.
View Cart
Checkout
Categories
Pleaser Brand - ExoticPleaser Pink Label - Large SizesPleaser Bordello - BurlesquePleaser Demonia - AlternativePleaser Devious - Fetish HeelsPleaser Fabulicious - SpecialPleaser Funtasma - CostumePleaser Pin Up Conture - VentagePleaser Day & Night - Close OutBettie Page ShoesEllie Shoes and BootsEllie 3 inchEllie 4 inchEllie 5 inchEllie 6 inchEllie 7 inchEllie 8 inchEllie Ankle BootsEllie Knee BootsEllie Thigh High BootsAll High Heel ShoesFlats3 3/4" and Lower4 inch high heels4 1/2 inch high heels5 inch high heels5 1/4 inch high heels5 1/2 inch high heels5 3/4 inch high heels6 inch high heels6 1/2 inch high heels6 3/4 inch high heels7 inch high heels7 1/2 inch high heels8 inch and higherAll High Heel BootsAnkle BootsMid Calf BootsKnee High BootsThigh High BootsCrotch BootsValentine's Day HeelsAllure Leather LingerieLeg Avenue CostumesAnimalsBees and BugsClownsCostume AccessoriesFairytale & FantasyHalloween FunHolidayInternational BeautiesMen's CostumesMiscellaneousMonsters & DragonsNinjasPiratesPlus SizeSchool GirlsSpooky ClassicsUniformsWarriors & Goddess'Lingerie by G WorldHigh Heels for MenWalk a Mile in Her Shoes®Karo' Shoes - Made in the USA4 Inch Heels and Lower5 Inch Heel Shoes6 Inch Heel Shoes7 Inch Heel Shoes8 Inch Heel ShoesSexy BootsFetish ShoesRed White and Blue ShoesLight and Glow in the Dark ShoesHot
Sticker CollectionsWide Width High HeelsX - Large Heels (sizes 15-17)* CLEARANCE *Clearance Size 5Clearance Size 6Clearance Size 7Clearance Size 8Clearance Size 9Clearance Size 10Clearance Size 11Clearance Size 12Clearance Size 13Clearance Size 14Clearance Size 15Clearance Size 16Clearance Size 17Clearance ApparelClearance StockingsClearance JewelryWedge SandalsSteampunk StyleAccessories...Specials ...New Products ...Featured Products ...All Products ...
Search
Advanced Search
Specials -   [more]
FAB-422 Red Satin 2" Heel Peep Toe Pump$45.95  $39.96
ASPIRE-608LN Clr/Blk 6" Heel, 2 1/4" Lined PF Ankle Strap Sandal$50.95  $46.96
New Products -   [more]
BEJEWELED-1018C-2RS Clr/Slv RS 7" Heel, 2 3/4" PF Open Toe/Heel $157.95
BEJEWELED-724RS Clr/Slv RS 7" Heel, 2 3/4" PF Ankle Cuff Sandal $139.95
BEYOND-008 Clr-Blk/Clr 10" Heel, 6 1/4" PF Ankle Strap Sandal$95.95
Reviews -   [more]
Should have a 6 in heel and it would be perfect and more...
Featured -   [more]
TEEZE-42W Blk Faux Leather 5 3/4" Heel, 1 3/4" PF Strappy T-Stra$81.95
TEEZE-42W Brown Faux Leather 5 3/4" Heel, 1 3/4" PF Strappy T-St$81.95
Bestsellers
VANITY-420 Fiery...
TEEZE-06W BLACK PAT...
KITTEN-01 Red Pat 2...
VANITY-420 Baby...
SEDUCE-420V Red...
BELLE-309 Blk/Blk...
DIVINE-420 Black PU...
AMOUR-03 Black...
VANITY-420 Black...
DREAM-420 Hot Pink...
Information
Shipping & Returns
Privacy Notice
Contact Us
Site Map
Discount Coupons
Useful Information
Email List Subscribe
Shoe Size Chart
Leather Knee High Boots
Eco-Friendly Cork Sandals and Shoes
Cork Sandals: A Shoe Staple from Ancient Rome to Modern Times
How to Look Sexy with Mary Jane Shoes
Get Your Sex Appeal a Notch Higher
Gogo Boots
High Heel Ankle Boots
Steampunk Boots Today
Searching For Large Sizes?
Sexy Extreme Heels
Drag In The Shoes
More Information
Size Chart
Thigh High Boots
Spring-o-lators
Sponsors
Home ::
Privacy Notice
Privacy Notice
Policies For Affections
and Heels For You
Listed below are our policies dealing with Security, Satisfaction Guarantee, and Privacy. If you have any questions, please feel free to ask.
Please make sure the address you enter on you order is correct. If your address is incorrect and results in the delivery service (UPS, FedEx or DHL) having to redirect to another address you will be charge a $10.00 charge. The delivery service charges us for your mistake and we can no longer continue to adsorb this charge so, please make sure the billing address AND the shipping address is correct when you place your order.
Secure Shopping
When making an online purchase at Affections, we use a secure server. When your browser communicates with a secure server all information is encrypted, keeping it private. This technology makes it safer to transmit your credit card information over the Internet. To use this server, your Web browser must support SSL (Secure Socket Layers).
Only authorized Affections employees have access to stored information. We safeguard information according to established security standards and procedures, and we continually assess new technology for protecting information. Our employees are trained to understand and comply with these information principles.
Note: Your credit card may be billed under the name "Affections Gifts and Cards"
Satisfaction Guaranteed
100% Satisfaction Guarantee - Inspect your order promptly! If for any reason you are not satisfied with your purchase from Affections, you MUST contact us within ten (10) days of receipt of your order to request a Return Authorization number (RMA #).
We MUST receive your merchandise along with the RMA number written on the outside of the package within 15 days from the date of the RMA #. Unauthorized returns, returns without a RMA #, or returns that are received later than 15 days after the RMA # was issued are subject to a 25% restocking fee.
There are no restocking fees for an exchanges or request for store credit. There is a 15% restocking fee applied to all returns requesting a refund. Shipping charges for the returns and exchanges are the responsibility of the customer. On exchanges, shipping will be figure according to the weight of the replacement items. (This usually runs approximately the amount paid for shipping from the original order). All exchange orders will be shipped Ground shipping unless requested otherwise & then shipping cost will be adjusted accordingly.
If at any time you find a defect of any kind on merchandise you have purchased from Affections or if you receive an item that is not what you ordered, please send a brief email describing the defect and we will send a replacement item, free of charge and arrange for the return of the defective item or wrong item. If you receive the wrong item please tell us what you received including item #, size & color. No additional shipping will be charged for replacing defective items or if the item received was incorrect.
Non-refundable items:
* Custom made items are NOT returnable unless defective, except for replacement, if defective.
* Item marked as Clearance - Sale Final are not refundable
* Wigs, undergarments including swimsuits, thongs, underwear, body stockings, lingerie and body jewelry are not returnable unless defective. (Due to health codes.)
* Stockings and pantyhose are not returnable once they have been removed from their original packages.
* Personal items such as sex toys or other adult products (this includes DVD's & VHS Tapes) are not returnable unless defective. Defective items will be replaced with same item only.
* Special Orders - Made to Order and Custom Made Orders take longer to be ready to ship. Approximate order processing times are posted on our web sites for these items.
See Our Return Policy - Request Return Authorization
Privacy Statement
Your Privacy
At Affections, we are committed to protecting your privacy online. Our pledge is to safeguard any information we collect associated with you and your name, and will make every reasonable effort to use this information only as you request.
Collecting and Using Your Information
When you make an online purchase, the information you provide allows us to process and fulfill your order, and to notify you of your order status. We need to know your name, email address, billing and mailing addresses which is stored along with a record of the products you purchase. We also need to know your credit card number, expiration date and gift recipient information. Once an online order has been confirmed, credit card information and gift recipient information is not reused.
When you submit a question or comment in a guestbook, we ask for your email address, name and country of residence. This allows us to route your message to the appropriate support staff to provide you a reply.
When you enter a sweepstakes or other promotional feature, we may ask for your name, address, and email address so we can administer the contest and notify the winners.
Protecting Your Information
Only authorized Affections employees have access to stored information. We safeguard information according to established security standards and procedures, and we continually assess new technology for protecting information. Our employees are trained to understand and comply with these information principles.
Affections will not sell, trade, or rent your personal information collected online to others (third parties).
How We Recognize You
In general, you can visit HeelsForYou.com without revealing any information about yourself. It is our intent to let you know before we collect any information from you online.
Our site is not setup to track, collect or distribute personal information about you unless you are a registered member. We cannot, for instance, determine your email address by examining electronic records. We use the electronic records to compile statistics that about how collectively our visitors interact with our Web site. These statistics contain no personal information and are only used by Affections technical support staff.
Send Us Your Feedback
If you have concerns about your privacy with the Heels For You web site, please tell us by submitting an email to info@affections.com. We will make every reasonable effort to address your concerns.
We acceptContact InformationSite InformationDeliveries & ReturnsSocial Media
Melissa, TX USA
info@affections.comHomeFeatured ProductsSpecialsNew ProductsAll Products ...
::
My Account
::
Shipping & Returns
::
Contact Us
::
My Account
::
Shipping & Returns
::
Contact Us
Desktop Version
Copyright © 2020 Heels For You. Powered by Zen Cart
Your IP Address is:
72.182.10.230
